{"status":"Success","data":{"quiz_datas":[{"question_no":"281","question":"\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d42\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d21\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7b","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d17\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"421","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02","option1":"20","option2":"27","option3":"44","option4":"40","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"390","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f 20-\u0d09\u0d2a\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2c\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d28\u0d02 :","option1":"PSLV 34-A","option2":"PSLV 33-C","option3":"PSLV 34-C","option4":"PSLV 33-A","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"683","question":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d15\u0d24 \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02, \u0d38\u0d41\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37 \u0d07\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d47 \u0d38\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d24\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d02","option1":"\u0d38\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d7c \u0d1f\u0d46\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d02","option2":"\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d38\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"566","question":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d7d ?","option1":"\u0d05\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e","option2":"\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d7c","option3":"\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02","option4":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d02","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"597","question":"\u0d38\u0d57\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d25\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d02","option1":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d36\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b","option3":"\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d38\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d27\u0d7b","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"17","question":"\u0d38\u0d3f.\u0d2c\u0d3f.\u0d10 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02?","option1":"\u0d38\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d31\u0d4b \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d","option2":"\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d\u200c \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d","option3":"\u0d38\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d","option4":"\u0d38\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d31\u0d4b \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"34","question":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d","option3":"\u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d26\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"186","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d07\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?","option1":"1992","option2":"1991","option3":"2007","option4":"2000","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"12","question":"1776 \u0d1c\u0d42\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d\u200c \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d12\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d35\u0d46\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41","option3":"\u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d36 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d28\u0d02","option4":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d40\u0d34\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f","answer":"1"}]},"code":"100"}
